Oh, see? It's so beautiful.
You look so fresh now.
You don't look
like a maid of honor.
[HANNAH] Is Kpaps going to
sell me to foreigners?
I mean, what kind
of translator...
is this pretty?
Pose. Go, keep going.
[RIA] So pretty! Very fresh!
She's so pretty. Yes!
Pose! Yes!
What a beautiful lady!
[GRUNTS]
Oh.
You look pretty...
for someone who scrubs floors.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Madam.
I don't want
to fight today, okay?
First of all, Daniel's not here.
And secondly,
I'm too pretty today.
[CHUCKLES DRYLY]
Fight?
No!
- I'm here to do laundry!
- Hey! Hey!
- [RIA] Miss... Hey!
- [HANNAH SCREAMING]
Stop it! Hey!
- Hey!
- Funny thing about laundry...
- Some stains...
- [HANNAH COUGHS]
- ...never leave!
- Stop--
[RIA] Stop! Brenda!
- [BRENDA LAUGHING]
- [HANNAH COUGHING]
You like that, huh?
Oh, you want to do this, huh?
[BRENDA SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS] Aah!
Do you hear the words
coming out of your mouth?!
You need to freshen up!
- [SCREAMS]
- Wash off that personality!
If I weren't in heels,
I swear...
You stay away from Daniel!
He's mine!
Fine!
Then you can have him
for all I care!
[BRENDA SCREAMS]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[HUFFING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [RIA SCREAMS]
What are you doing?
[BRENDA SCREAMS]
I didn't do anything.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]